&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：最强大的工具之一
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: One of
the most powerful tools for
这些天的变压器代码是巴别塔。
a transformer code these days is Babel.
巴别塔也有一些优点和缺点。
And Babel has some ups and downsides.
我想快速谈谈的是
What I kind of wanna talk
about real quick is this
这个想法有时叫做缴纳巴别税，对吧？
idea sometimes called paying
the Babel tax, right?
巴别塔，对于那些不知道的人来说，
Babel, for those of you who don't know,
是一个基本上允许我们编写未来JavaScript并转换它的工具
is a tool that basically allows us to
write future JavaScript and transpile it
转换为JavaScript，它可以在较旧的浏览器中工作，有时也可以在现代浏览器中工作。
into JavaScript that will work in older
browsers and sometimes modern browsers.
我们以前看过import语法，从技术上讲它还不是该语言中的语法，但是
We saw the import syntax before, it's
not technically in the language yet, but
我可以用它。
I could use it.
因为巴贝尔会让我写未来的JavaScript
Because Babel will let me
write future JavaScript,
将其转换为可以在今天的浏览器中工作的JavaScript。
turn it into JavaScript that
will work in today's browsers.
或者将今天的JavaScript转换为可以在以前的浏览器中使用的JavaScript。
Or turn today's JavaScript into JavaScript
that'll work in previous browsers.
当我还是个孩子的时候，你不能使用所有很酷的JavaScript功能，因为IE6
When I was a kid, you couldn't use all
the cool JavaScript features cuz IE6
不支持他们对吧？
didn't support them, right?
你知道有这样更好的生活，你不能因此[笑]。
You knew there was this better life that
you couldn't have [LAUGH] because of this.
所以在很多情况下仍然是这样，但是事实是我们可以，
So that still is the case in a lot of
cases, but the fact that we can then,
在幕后，把它转换成能工作的代码真的很棒
behind the scenes, turn it into
code that works is really great and
让我们动作真的很快，让Web开发变得更好。
lets us really kind of move quickly and
makes web development a lot better.
但这并不总是免费的，有时也是一种权衡。
But this isn't always free,
and it's sometimes a tradeoff.
所以我想向你们展示的是我在这里有一个小小的回购。
So what I wanna kinda show you is
I have this little repo in here.
让我们真的杀了这个吧。
Let's actually kill this one.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：实际上我会在浏览器中拉出它。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I'm actually
gonna pull it up in a browser.
如果你去巴别塔，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们说，
If you go to Babel,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And we say,
尝试一下，你可以看到这个小repl，你可以在这里输入一些代码，然后
try it out, you can see this little repl
where you can type in some code, and
您将看到另一端弹出的代码。
you'll see code that
pops out the other end.
所以，我们可以看到一些相对简单的事情，比如好的，
And so, we can see some relatively
simple things, like okay,
我可以有，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：一个数组，
I can have,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: An array,
让我们把这个字体做大一点，不要那么大。
let's make this font a little bigger,
not that big.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：如果我们使用4H，我们可以说array.4H，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And if we use a 4H,
we can say array.4H,
我可以使用花哨的箭头语法，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：哪个
I can use a fancy arrow syntax,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Which
在某些浏览器中不受支持。
is not supported in some browsers.
你可以看到它把它变成了更传统的语法。
And you can see it turns it into
the more traditional syntax.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我也可以使用全新的for of语法，可能像for
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I can also use a brand
new for of syntax, maybe like for
(字母数组数)。
(let number of array).
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：你在另一边注意到了什么？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: What do you
notice on the other side?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：更多代码。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: A lot more code.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：代码要多得多，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: It's a lot more code,
right?
这是更多的代码。
That is a lot more code.
这意味着这个代码必须被解析，
And that means this code has to be parsed,
这意味着这个代码必须被发送，对吗？
that means this code that
has to be shipped, right?
是的，这个语法很酷，对吧？
And yes,
this syntax is pretty cool, right?
我的一些其他浏览器也可以支持它，但有一点
And some of my other browsers can
support it, but there is a little
做这个决定，对吧，就像我们以前那样，对吧？
bit of making that decision, right,
the old way that we could, right?
JavaScript中的一些类就是说，功能点。
Some classes in JavaScript was to say,
function point.
嘿，又是那个例子。
Hey, it's that example again.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：等于x，因此。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Equals x, thus.
我想这将是我想在我的JavaScript中开始做的一件事，因此！
I think that's gonna be a thing I wanna
start doing in my JavaScript, thus!
[笑]那就随它去吧。
[LAUGH] So let it be.
所以我们可以有这样的函数，我们可以说新的点。
So we could have a function like this,
and we could say new point.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：这就像，在你的JavaScript中尝试一下，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And this is like,
try it into your JavaScript,
没什么可做的。
there's not a lot to do.
它真正做的就是在上面放一个ustrix语句。
All it really does is put
a ustrix statement on top.
如果我快速改变这个，我们说class
If I change this real quick though and
we say class
Point，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：你
point,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: You
已经可以看出这里有点失控了。
can already see this is getting
a little out of hand here.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：实际上，我认为我复制并粘贴了这些代码。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Actually,
I think I copy and paste that code.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们可以看到这是多行代码。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We can see
this is multiple lines of code.
对于你所做的每一堂课，这都会一遍又一遍地重复。
And that repeats over and
over for every class that you do.
你会有这条额外的线。
You'll have this extra line.
你会给你的文件增加更多，对吗？
You'll add more to your files, right?
所以有很多方法可以做到这一点。
So there's a bunch of ways to do this.
一种是类似箭头功能的东西，
One is kind of stuff like arrow functions,
这些是很好的模板字符串，不会创建很多代码。
those are nice template strings that
aren't gonna create a lot of code.
像Async Await这样的东西使用这个叫做再生器运行时的东西，
Things like async await use this
thing called regenerator runtime,
哪些是代码页，你要另外移动，对吗？
which is pages of code that you're
gonna shift in addition, right?
所以有时候，你必须权衡取舍，
So sometimes,
you have to weigh the trade offs,
它对你的捆绑包的大小有什么影响？
what is it doing to
the size of your bundle?
你怎么知道这是不是有问题？
And how do you figure out whether or
not this is problematic?
你量过的，对吧？
You measure it, right?
但是这些工具中的一些，并不是所有的东西都是免费的，如果你不用心的话，
But some of these tools, not everything
is free, and if you're not being mindful,
从理论上讲，你可以在很多这些东西上交税
you can theoretically end up paying
a tax on a lot of these things and
对你想做的事情有负面影响，对吧？
having adverse effects on what
you were trying to do, right?
所以一直保持关注是很重要的
So it's always important to
just kind of keep an eye and
测量很多这些东西。
measure a lot of these things.